DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
SOME SCENES WERE GENERATED USING AI
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
[♪ melancholy music playing]
I'm going to think of Seonu
every time I see you now.
It's going to
be like this forever, isn't it?
[chattering]
[machine beeping]
[breathes heavily]
Dr. Do, are you okay?
The patient's regained consciousness!
[whispering] I'm okay.
[announcer on PA speaks Korean]
Deokhwa…
What about Deokhwa?
[doctor] It's acute epiglottitis.
She's currently unresponsive
under sedation,
but depending on
her condition or progress,
we'll taper the dosage
to help her regain consciousness.
With acute epiglottitis,
we need to put her on antibiotics
and monitor her closely.
The concern is that potential
complications could lead to brain damage,
or in severe cases, even death.
[crying] No!
Oh, Deokhwa!
Doctor, please save Deokhwa.
My dear girl…
What the doctor just said
was the absolute worst-case scenario
that could happen.
We caught it early
and treated her right away.
And it's rare for a child
to suffer permanent brain damage,
so you don't need to worry too much.
But earlier on, the doctor said Deokhwa…
That's just what a doctor has to do.
Doctors have to be prepared
for the absolute worst-case scenarios,
just to ensure the patient gets
the best possible care.
[parent sniffles]
You should also get treated, ma'am.
Sorry? [sniffs]
I'm talking about your feet.
Oh, I'm perfectly fine.
I'm okay.
But something horrible
could have happened to you earlier
STYLE
::cue()
because of us, though.
I'm so sorry.
-I'm really sorry.
-[chuckles]
It's okay. I just passed out for a moment.
I'm fine.
-But…
-[stammering] Oh, I'm completely fine.
I'm totally okay. [chuckles]
[parent]
But you also fell in the water too.
[Hari] I'm fine.
[parent] Are you really okay?
[♪ surreal music playing]
EPISODE 5
PYEONDONG SCANDAL
Dr. Do.
-Yes?
-[parent sniffles]
Oh. [chuckles]
[parent cries]
Oh.
[elevator bell dinging]
[doors opening]
-[announcer speaks indistinctly on PA]
-Why'd you do it? It was dangerous.
It was nothing.
I'm a great swimmer.
I may not look it,
but I was born and raised on an island.
-But still--
-Jeez, what are you hesitating for?
Just thank me and be done with it.
We both made it out okay,
so that's all that matters.
Thank you.
[♪ soft music playing]
[automated voice] Basement One.
I also want to thank you.
You saved them both.
Deokhwa and her mom.
[doors closing]
[staff] Please make way.
-Coming through.
-[staff] Thank you.
[automated voice] The doors are closing.
[automated voice] First floor.
Hmm? Ms. Yuk Hari?
[gasps]
So it was you, Ms. Yuk Hari!
The nurses said
they ran into you in the ER,
and I told them there was no way.
But it is you!
Yes, well, it's a long story…
[nurse] You should have let us know
if you were coming.
But who's this next to you?
Ah, he's a doctor I work with.
[nurse] Oh.
A doctor you work with, huh?
Hello, I'm a nurse who used to
work with Ms. Yuk.
Yes. I'm Do Jiui.
We should get going now.
He's still a patient, so…
Let's go.
[♪ comical music playing]
[nurse] Yuk Hari came to the hospital.
With a guy.
STYLE
::cue()
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
[phone ringing]
Ms. Yuk?
[Hari] Yes. I made you worry, didn't I?
Deokhwa's being treated with antibiotics,
and Dr. Do is also okay.
What about you?
[chuckles]
-I'm also doing okay.
-[sighs]
What did she say?
We'll return as soon as
we get Dr. Do's results.
Okay. I'll let everyone know.
She said everyone's okay.
[sighs]
-[Ms. Hwang] Oh, what a relief.
-[breathes heavily]
We didn't hear back for so long,
I was afraid something happened to them.
I know, right? Me too.
Since she said everyone's all right,
let's all get back to work.
We're down two people today,
so let's get it together.
Okay.
[sighs]
[inhales sharply] Isn't it really weird?
He cares way too much about her.
Yes. Really weird.
Your test results are all clear,
but you do have a mild concussion.
You should stay the night at the hospital
for further monitoring.
Okay.
[exhales]
[stammers] Are you leaving?
Oh, no, I was just heading out
to the convenience store.
Oh.
Does it scare you a little
because you're here as a patient?
[sighs]
Just wait a little.
I'll be back before they give you a shot.
[register beeping, whirring]
[nurse 1] Did you hear?
I heard Yuk Hari's here.
She came in with that emergency patient
who fell overboard.
Wow. To think she came here
knowing that Dr. Dongseop's here.
-And with a guy. She's unbelievable.
-[nurse 1 chuckling]
I know, right?
What's even crazier is that
the guy's apparently a PH doc.
I guess the rumors are true.
That Yuk Hari is a doctor hunter.
[nurse 2] For sure.
[nurses giggling]
[nurse 1] Gosh, you have no idea.
It was a huge scandal here back then.
We all had to walk on eggshells…
Feel free to let me know
if there's anything you'd like to know.
I'll be going now.
[nurses whispering]
[objects clattering]
[patient] What do you mean,
you can't do it? Huh?
You're a doctor,
so do your job and treat me, okay?
STYLE
::cue()
What's going on?
Talk some sense into him, would you?
See this? I even took my shirt off,
but he suddenly says he won't
give me acupuncture treatment.
Don't you have a duty to treat a patient?
Why won't you say anything?
Say something, okay? Hey!
-[Jeongseon] Please let go and--
-Are you looking down on me?
-That's enough.
-What's this?
Trust me, you don't want to do this to me.
-[bones crack]
-[patient exclaims]
Interfering with medical care
or assaulting healthcare workers
is a serious crime.
Hey, you're the one who's assaulting me!
-Do you even know who I am? [strains]
-[bones cracking]
[Hyeon] I have no idea who you are.
Should I call the cops
so we can identify you?
[stammering] Hey, I get it.
Why call the cops all of a sudden?
Damn it.
Let go, I get it. [grunting]
Why you little… I work out, man.
Call the cops. Call whoever you want.
Screw that. You know what?
You can even call those punks in the US,
the NFS, for all I care, damn it!
-I'll kill every last one of them.
-Oh my, Mr. Yeom, what is it?
-What?
-I'm busy, so I'm heading out now.
[Ms. Hwang] What would
a bunch of young 'uns know?
-[objects clatter]
-I'll give them a proper scolding.
Oh, dear…
[Hyeon] That prick doesn't even know
what the NFS is.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Mr. Ko, sir! Yes.
The construction?
It's going very smoothly, sir.
Don't you worry. Yes, of course.
Two thousand won?
I'll be sure to wrap things up
within the deadline.
I understand, sir. You know me.
I'm Yeom Byeongcheol.
We've got plenty of time.
Yes. I understand.
I pledge my undying loyalty to you, sir!
Hey, isn't that Byeongcheol?
When did he get here?
I heard he's been put in charge
of the helipad construction project.
He must've cozied up
to some mainland big shots.
Helipad construction project?
Goodness.
Why are they tearing down
a perfectly functional helipad?
That guy's going to stir up trouble again.
This is driving me crazy.
What's gotten into you?
I was the one who examined Deokhwa first.
If I had examined her properly…
what happened to Deokhwa…
Dr. Jiui…
and Ms. Hari…
[sniffs]
…could have been prevented.
[breathes shakily]
I'm scared…
of treating my patients.
[sniffs, breathes heavily]
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ soft guitar music playing]
Aren't you hungry?
Well… A little.
[Hari exclaims]
-Let's dig in.
-Please, help yourself.
Do you like hamburgers?
Yes, I do.
I love everything about our clinic,
except that there are no burger places.
You must really like hamburgers.
Yes. It's my comfort food.
[chuckles]
Ever since I was little,
my grandma bought me hamburgers
whenever something bad happened.
When I got into a fight with a friend,
when I tanked an exam,
and even when I was scolded by my grandma.
You must be really close
with your grandmother.
We're super close.
[chuckles]
Ever since I was little,
my grandma was all I had in the world.
My grandma's my mom, my dad, my friend,
and everything.
She's my everything.
[chuckles]
[exclaims]
-You've got ketchup on you.
-[grunts]
Um…
-Thank you.
-[Hari] Right there.
[Jiui grunts]
[nurse 1] I guess the rumors are true.
That Yuk Hari is a doctor hunter.
[♪ soft music playing]
Feel free to let me know
if there's anything you'd like to know.
Hey, Dr. Do…
Did you…
Never mind.
Um…
I'm done eating, so I'll get going now.
The ferries have probably
stopped running though.
I'll just get a room.
Let's meet at the port tomorrow.
Ms. Yuk…
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[sighs]
-Hari.
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
-[panting]
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I called you so many times.
Do you know how worried I was?
I heard you transferred to an island.
How are things there?
I'd been meaning to visit you, but…
Looks like you've been doing well.
You look good.
I haven't been doing so great.
I've been thinking about you a lot.
Yeah, I could tell.
They're still gossiping about me here.
Apparently,
I'm a doctor-hunter gold digger.
[exhales]
Well, people are misunderstanding
because I'm struggling so--
Misunderstanding?
I assume that was your intention.
I'm sure you made me the bad guy,
so you can look like a good guy.
Hari.
Let's stop fighting now.
I told you I was sorry.
We're not fighting. We broke up, okay?
What do you mean, "we broke up"?
I'm not breaking up with you!
I told you I'm not breaking up with you.
Why? Is it because of
that PH doc you came here with?
Is that prick better than me? Huh?
So you want to move on with him?
Forget it. I have nothing to say to you.
Where do you think you're going?
How dare you?
I'm not done talking to you.
[Hari] Dr. Do!
Who the hell are you?
Oh, so you're the PH doc
she came here with?
[grunts]
-Dr. Do, let go.
-[Dongseop grunts]
[Hari] Let's just go.
There's nothing more to be said.
You better snap out of it!
She's not really into you.
She's dated three doctors here,
including me!
She jumps ship
the second someone better comes along.
She's a gold digger.
I'm saying she's got her hooks in you!
I don't care
if she's a gold digger or not.
I've been begging her
to get her hooks in me, actually.
What?
Sheesh.
But honestly, it's a huge relief.
Because anyone with eyes
can see who the better man is.
So know your place and get lost, will you?
You and I don't belong in the same league.
Let's go, Ms. Yuk.
-What?
-[nurse 1] What was that?
STYLE
::cue()
[nurse 2] Did he just get dumped?
[nurse 3] Then it's his second time
getting dumped.
[sighs, mutters]
I'm sorry you had to get involved
in my messy affair.
There's nothing messy about it.
That's on them.
Didn't you hear all about me
from Ms. Sujeong earlier on?
No, I didn't hear a thing she said.
It all sounded like useless drivel anyway.
I dated people and broke up with them,
just like everyone else…
but people called me
a doctor-hunter gold digger.
I didn't take you for the type
to let such rumors get to you.
I didn't think so myself.
I thought I didn't care about
what people said behind my back,
since they knew nothing about
who I really am.
[♪ soft guitar music playing]
But I guess I was just acting tough.
Seeing you alone with Ms. Sujeong earlier…
really scared me.
I was worried you might also
start believing those rumors about me.
[chuckles]
And it felt like you were
keeping your distance from me, and…
that just made me mad and scared.
So about what happened earlier, I…
I know. I was just paranoid
because my conscience got the best of me.
[chuckles]
I pretended I came
to Pyeondongdo for my grandma…
But to be honest, I ran away so I could
find comfort in her embrace.
Like a coward.
Everyone runs…
when the pain gets unbearable.
I also run away a lot.
Want me to buy you a burger?
What?
I actually know
a great burger joint nearby.
[laughing]
I know you didn't even finish
half your burger earlier.
You're right.
Get some rest. I'll be going now.
-Are you going?
-Huh?
I mean, what kind of nurse
just leaves a patient behind?
I told you. This is my first time
being treated as a patient, so…
I'm really scared.
[♪ comical music playing]
[both chuckle]
STYLE
::cue()
Mother.
[grandmother] Hello?
Had anything to eat yet?
[sobbing] Yes, Deokhwa already ate.
I was asking about you, not Deokhwa.
Have you had anything to eat yet?
[parent] I'm sorry, Mother.
Goodness, stop crying.
You saved Deokhwa's life.
Be sure to eat well
and go straight to bed. Okay.
Isn't it such a relief?
-They all made it out alive.
-Gosh, I know.
This is all thanks to you, Mr. Park.
Come now, I can't take the credit.
The real hero is Ms. Hari.
She flung herself into
the pitch-black waters just like that.
The more I think about it,
the more amazed I am.
She dived right in
without a moment of hesitation.
What's this about Hari
diving into the water?
Mija, the thing is…
Hey, what were you talking about just now?
What do you mean,
Hari flung herself into the water?
Well, you see--
So, Hari wasn't simply
accompanying them to the hospital.
She ended up going
because she fell into the sea?
Mija, you see--
I mean, how could no one
talk her out of doing something like that?
[Mr. Park] We had no time
to talk her out of it.
She dived in to save Dr. Do
the moment he went overboard.
You still should have
talked her out of it!
My goodness.
What was she thinking,
jumping into the sea like that?
Hari, what were you thinking? [gasps]
[grunting]
[groans]
-[grunts]
-Huh?
[Mija groans]
-Are you okay, ma'am?
-[panting]
[Hyeon] It's a painkiller.
I'm sure the stress caused the migraines.
[sighs]
[sniffs]
I'll have you know I'm not particularly
fond of the public health center, either.
You've got young doctors and two nurses
other than Hari, but of all people,
you sent my precious granddaughter
in the middle of the night…
I'm sorry, ma'am.
And while we're on the subject,
let me ask you something else.
Do you like Hari?
[chuckles]
I know what the villagers have been saying
about you and Hari.
That's another thing
that really bothers me,
so please stop sending her false signals
by pretending that you care about her.
I wasn't pretending.
What now?
You sleep here, Ms. Yuk.
[stammers] No way.
You're the patient here.
So listen to the patient.
Do you want to stress out the patient?
-Absolutely not. Hurry up and lie down.
-[patient] For goodness' sake.
Keep it down, will you?
See that? Are you seriously
going to stress out your patient?
-Hurry up and lie down.
-[stammers]
Seriously…
[Jiui grunting]
Whatever. I'm already lying down.
[Hari sighs]
[whispering] See? It's too small for you.
-You'll be uncomfortable.
-[whispering] I'll be fine.
-Seriously…
-[Jiui chuckles]
Ms. Hari.
Yes?
Earlier on…
[patient coughs, clearing throat]
Never mind.
Good night.
A BEAUTIFUL YEOPOONG,
HAPPY RESIDENTS
[Changmok] Crap, I didn't cut it straight.
You handled the Pyeondongdo matter
as I said, right?
STYLE
::cue()
I'm afraid taking disciplinary action
against the PH doc
isn't really an option.
What nonsense is this now?
There was an incident
on the day I arrived.
There was a medical emergency
involving a child,
but the PH doc
who was due to receive the warning,
risked his life to save her.
Issuing a warning to a doctor like that
would have had a negative impact
on their morale, so--
Hold on, so you're saying
the Pyeondongdo PH doc
risked his life to save a child's life?
Yes.
Well, in that case,
I'll have to meet up with that PH doc.
What?
Don't you get it?
That's exactly
the kind of story I could use
as someone who dreams
of modernizing health care.
Try to keep up.
[inhales sharply]
Yes. I should meet him.
ASONG UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
[employee]
Here's your prescription and receipt.
[Hari] Should we go now?
Sure.
The ferry's about to leave, so…
I guess you're on your way now.
Yes.
You must've really settled in
on the island, Ms. Hari.
Seeing you thrive like this
is such a relief.
It really is a relief.
Ms. Sujeong.
I want you to know that I liked you all.
I wanted to get along with everyone,
and I wanted to work harder
to make you like me
and to dispel all those weird rumors.
But things didn't work out,
and that really bothered me.
But leaving made me realize something.
"I'm glad I left this dump."
[both scoff]
Ms. Yuk Hari!
And one more thing.
If you mess with me again,
I'm seriously going to kill you.
Let's go.
Oh, okay.
[nurse scoffs]
[gasps]
[Ms. Hwang] What's this? Oh, goodness.
We'll be feasting on this until next year.
-[chuckles]
-What's all this?
I don't know how the villagers found out
Dr. Do was getting discharged,
but it's been crazy since this morning.
They brought in every healthy food
imaginable from land, sea, and air.
We could throw a whole feast.
But why is everyone
only looking for Dr. Do?
There's someone else who needs to recover.
-Huh?
-It's nothing.
-I'll move all these.
-Put them in the fridge.
[grunts, exclaims]
[gasps] Oh, what happened?
Ms. Eom! Jeongseon, where does it hurt?
[Jeongseon winces] That hurts…
That spot doesn't hurt.
How does it look?
[Hyeon] Hmm…
It looks like you sprained your ankle.
I'll prescribe some Enstaid for you.
-That's not an option.
-Huh?
I get side effects when I take steroids.
Then you should get it treated
at the Korean Medicine Ward.
The Korean Medicine Ward?
Um, me?
I think getting it treated on the mainland
might be the better option.
Why's that?
It looks like minor inflammation now,
but it could be something more serious,
even a fracture.
You should go to a hospital
on the mainland to get a proper diagnosis…
Why would I do that?
I have a doctor of Korean Medicine here,
so why would I spend money
and time to go to the mainland?
I'm just going to get it treated here.
-Ms. Eom.
-What?
Are you too scared to treat it?
Then just leave it be.
I'll just try toughing it out.
You really shouldn't be moving around--
I guess I'll just drag my foot around.
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[announcer] The ship bound for
Pyeondongdo, Pyeondongdo is now departing.
Are you really going to be okay?
[sighs] No.
If you need your meds,
we can go back to the hospital to--
But you said we should give this a go.
While holding your hand.
Uh…
[ship horn blows]
If I get too scared,
I'll just hold your hand.
Hmm.
Shall we go?
[Hari whimpers]
If you're so worried about me…
That thing you played…
Let me listen to it again.
What do you mean?
The song you played for me back then.
When you said music helps treat anxiety.
I couldn't find it
no matter how hard I looked.
You actually looked it up?
I just figured it might be
some special music or something…
[groans] And to think you were being
so difficult with me back then.
Give me a second.
[seagulls squawking]
[♪ "This is How Love Begins" playing]
YEOPOONG MARINE TRANSPORT
[song continues]
[song ends]
[Jeongseon grunts]
[exclaims]
I must be getting old.
My skin keeps breaking out.
[Jucheon] It's so swollen.
Ms. Eom, please stop being so stubborn
and hurry over to a hospital, okay?
I'm not going.
If you leave the inflammation untreated,
it could become chronic.
Something you'll deal with all your life.
Which is why you can just patch me up.
What the heck is the matter with you?
I told you I'm scared, didn't I?
If I were to mistreat someone--
[Jeongseon] Goodness, Dr. Yong.
You know you're beating yourself up
for no reason, right?
What?
Deokhwa was diagnosed
with acute epiglottitis.
Not even Heo Jun…
I mean, not even the greatest doctor
in history could have seen that coming.
But still…
What are you even doing here
if you're not going to do anything?
If you're going to whine and ignore people
over one misdiagnosis,
what's the point of you being here?
STYLE
::cue()
Nobody's asking you to play God
and perform miracles, okay?
Stop overthinking and just do your job.
[clicks tongue]
So just hurry up and do something
about my leg. It's killing me!
Hurry.
It's not like I have any medicine to take.
You're doing this
because you feel bad for me, right?
What's this nonsense now?
[clicks tongue]
[sighs]
I know you don't have side effects
from steroids.
That medicine you applied earlier…
It was a corticosteroid.
[♪ soft music playing]
[Jeongseon] Hmm.
But I'll still give it a shot,
since you trusted me.
Please do.
And hurry because I really am
in a lot of pain.
[Jucheon sighs]
Just a moment.
-[Jeongseon] Cheers.
-[Jucheon] Cheers.
[groans]
-The thing about me is…
-Hmm.
…I'm actually not a talkative person.
-You?
-Yeah.
I became talkative because I wanted people
to like me so badly,
and now I can't keep my mouth shut.
[Jeongseon groaning]
That's so sad.
-[groans]
-Hmm.
Isn't it?
So I'm asking you to look out for me.
Hmm. Okay!
[grunts]
[Jucheon] Hmm.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You just asked me to look out for you.
-[Jucheon] All done, Ms. Eom.
-Huh?
-Why don't you try getting up slowly?
-[groans]
How is it? Feeling better now, right?
Look how good you are at this.
All that whining for nothing.
[groans]
Thank you.
Oh, Ms. Eom.
Yes?
Keep Mondays, Wednesdays,
and Fridays open for me.
Huh?
[♪ romantic music playing]
For your acupuncture treatment.
Fine by me.
[breathes heavily]
Why the hell is my heart beating so fast?
I thought for sure he'd hear it.
STYLE
::cue()
[ship horn blows]
Huh?
[panting]
Dr. Do. Dr. Do, uh…
[breathes heavily]
[Hari gasps]
[♪ soft music playing]
[breathes heavily]
[groans]
[Hari] Let's go to the quarters together.
I'll take you there.
Oh, no, it's fine.
Let me come with you. I'm just worried.
I'm really feeling better now.
[exhales]
[Hari] Huh?
Uh, Grandma!
What are you doing out here, huh?
Come with me.
[Hari] What is it? Is something wrong?
I said, come with me!
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I put Ms. Yuk in danger.
I'm sorry to make you worry like that.
I don't give a damn if you fall
into the ocean, or if you live or die.
It's got nothing to do with me.
I'm just terrified that Hari is going to
throw herself into danger again.
Grandma, it wasn't because of Dr. Do.
That was on me, okay?
And besides,
it wasn't even that dangerous.
Listen to yourself, you brat!
[grunts]
-Grandma!
-[Jiui] Oh, no!
[Hari] Grandma!
We should get her to the center.
Right, okay.
[Jiui panting]
[grunts]
PYEONDONGDO FISHERIES
COOPERATIVE
STYLE
::cue()
What the… [grunts]
Is that Mija?
Goodness me, what happened?
We have to get her to a hospital.
It's a breast cancer patient
with possible brain metastasis.
BREAST CANCER:
CANCER IN THE BREAST
BRAIN METASTASIS:
CANCER SPREAD TO BRAIN
[Hari] Grandma.
-Hurry!
-[Jeongseon] Yes, I'm on it.
Granny Mija has breast cancer?
It's okay. I feel fine.
[Mija grunts]
Let's get you to a hospital, okay?
Oh, I'm fine.
Ma'am, migraines are a bad sign.
We should get you to a hospital
for a checkup…
I said you don't have to worry about me.
I'll be fine.
No, Grandma.
Oh, my baby.
-I'm fine, okay?
-No.
-I'm fine.
-[crying]
[Mija] Let's just go home, okay?
Goodness.
What's going on?
Is it bad?
I'm okay.
Oh, my baby. Let's go home, okay?
[groans, chuckles]
I'm okay.
[chuckles]
My baby, I'm okay.
-Grandma.
-My baby.
[groans]
I'm okay. Okay?
Let's hurry up and go home, my baby.
[Hari crying] No.
[Mija] Goodness, I'm fine.
How long have you known, Dr. Do?
What?
Shouldn't you share
crucial patient information?
[Jiui sighs]
I prescribed painkillers
for Ms. Oh Mija yesterday.
Had I known, I would have given her
a proper prescription
or done something.
There's nothing you could have done
even if you knew.
She's on Chavoxifen.
She has stage four cancer.
And the patient herself…
didn't want people to find out about it.
Not that it matters now.
STYLE
::cue()
[Hari] Here.
Let's have some of your favorite pasta.
[Mija] Hmm.
[Hari] Hmm.
[slurping]
Hari.
It was just a one-time thing.
I'm really okay.
I know you're okay, Grandma.
[sniffs]
[♪ mournful music playing]
[sniffing continues]
[slurping]
MS. YUK HARI
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[knocks on door]
Yes?
BOJUNGIKGITANG
What's this?
It's a herbal medicine.
It works wonders for fatigue.
Oh, thank you.
Um, I'm sorry.
I'm well aware
how there was no way I could have detected
Deokhwa's acute epiglottitis.
I know I just need to focus
on doing my job.
But regardless, I'm really sorry.
To you, to Ms. Hari,
and to Deokhwa as well.
So please be sure to have it.
It'll bring out the tiger in you.
Oh.
Get some rest.
Bring out the tiger…
[crickets chirping]
Is this a little too corny?
STYLE
::cue()
[Hari sniffs]
[sighs]
I'm sure there was more to the situation.
[ship horn blows]
[exhales]
How's your grandma?
-She's a lot better now.
-Hmm.
The center will also
take special care of her,
so don't worry too much. Okay?
-[chuckles] Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
-Ms. Yuk, can we talk for a moment?
-Huh?
Oh, sure.
[sighs]
[exhales]
Could you close the door while you look?
It's made of glass for a reason, you know.
Of course. That's why it's made of glass.
These. How much are these two?
-Don't worry about it.
-Huh?
I might run a shop, but I'm not heartless.
You saved Deokhwa's life.
There's no way I'm taking your money.
No, you should still let me pay.
No, it's fine.
Just take it so I can bum a drink off you.
Does that mean it's free for me too?
Sure, why not.
Score!
Hold on a minute.
Since you're here,
you should take this with you.
Hold on, this…
You cleaned out the whole shelf
when you came by yesterday,
so I figured you loved 'em
and saved some more for you.
-[chuckles]
-[Jiui] I see.
I didn't know you liked gummies.
I'll be going now. Thank you for this.
-Yes.
-Right.
Oh, my.
[chuckles]
-Granny, I'm off.
-Okay.
♪ I ought to grab a beer with him ♪
STYLE
::cue()
[chuckles]
So you like these too, huh?
It's not like that.
Wait. Did you get these for me?
Because they're shaped like burgers?
Hmm.
[chuckles]
But why didn't you give them to me?
I needed these yesterday.
It's not that I didn't. I couldn't, okay?
Why's that?
Last night…
I saw you with Dr. Chiyeon…
in front of your house.
It seemed like you two were having
an important conversation, so…
Oh, there's something
I needed to tell you.
[coughing]
-[stammers] What is it?
-Huh?
Oh, Dr. Chiyeon said
he's going to find a way
for my grandma to get approved
for a clinical trial.
Isn't that great?
-Really?
-Yes.
[sighs]
And to think I thought you guys were…
To think you thought we were, what?
Come on! What did you think
was happening between us?
Well, the two of you
seemed really close, so I…
Were you jealous?
[chuckles]
No, I wasn't jealous or anything.
Come on.
I'm pretty sure you were jealous.
-You were jealous, weren't you?
-Come on. Why would I be jealous?
[Hari chuckles]
I was just teasing you. [chuckles]
It's not like I have any right
to be jealous.
You said you would
never get your hooks into me.
[Hari] Hmm.
Remember what you said at the hospital?
How it felt like
I was keeping my distance?
Yes, you were right.
I was keeping my distance from you.
In case you caught on.
[♪ romantic music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
But why won't you get your hooks into me?
If there's something you don't like
about me, tell me. I'll fix it.
[♪ romantic song playing]
I just got my hooks in.
Where do we go from here?
[waves crashing]
[song continues]
EVERYONE RUNS
WHEN THE PAIN GETS UNBEARABLE
I ALSO RUN AWAY A LOT
JUCHEON:
THERE'S A LOT OF TENSION IN THE AIR
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE?
JEONGSEON:
I WAS ALREADY OVERWHELMED,
AND DEALING WITH YOUR GLARE
MADE IT EVEN HARDER
PERFECT LIGHTING IS
OUR WAY OF LOVING THE ACTORS
[song ends]
DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
[Hari] Today is officially day one for us.
[Mija] Don't you know there are always
people watching on this tiny island?
Ms. Yuk Hari.
Pick a side and stick to it.
I'm asking whose side you're on, okay?
[Ms. Hwang] Are you fighting again?
Now that you know, do it.
No! I can't do it!
Can we talk for a moment?
[Hari] Dr. Do.
It says you're to report
to Yeopoong-gun starting tomorrow.
Translated by Yoon Hyuk Park